[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "But, Wolf, let me -- does Congress realize just how ridiculous it appears to the rest of the world?", "question_tokens": ["But", ",", "Wolf", ",", "let", "me", "--", "does", "Congress", "realize", "just", "how", "ridiculous", "it", "appears", "to", "the", "rest", "of", "the", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "It depends on, you know, who you're talking to.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "depends", "on", ",", "you", "know", ",", "who", "you", "'re", "talking", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"], "PERSON": ["Wolf"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "Is this just as John McCain said to me, the same movie being replayed?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "just", "as", "John", "McCain", "said", "to", "me", ",", "the", "same", "movie", "being", "replayed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "The Republicans by all accounts are being blamed more than the Democrats from this including in our brand new CNN poll that just came out today.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "Republicans", "by", "all", "accounts", "are", "being", "blamed", "more", "than", "the", "Democrats", "from", "this", "including", "in", "our", "brand", "new", "CNN", "poll", "that", "just", "came", "out", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John McCain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "WP", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "Who's to blame, how long will it last?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "to", "blame", ",", "how", "long", "will", "it", "last", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "Who's to blame, we're going to see what happens and whether or not that the reality matches the polls beforehand and the fear among Republicans frankly that they are the ones who are going to get the blames.", "answer_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "to", "blame", ",", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "see", "what", "happens", "and", "whether", "or", "not", "that", "the", "reality", "matches", "the", "polls", "beforehand", "and", "the", "fear", "among", "Republicans", "frankly", "that", "they", "are", "the", "ones", "who", "are", "going", "to", "get", "the", "blames", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Armed Forces", "Piers", "Congress"]}, "docId": "130930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "EX", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "Jim Acosta, down the White House, have we heard anything from the White House of the President other than the video we saw that he gave to the military?", "question_tokens": ["Jim", "Acosta", ",", "down", "the", "White", "House", ",", "have", "we", "heard", "anything", "from", "the", "White", "House", "of", "the", "President", "other", "than", "the", "video", "we", "saw", "that", "he", "gave", "to", "the", "military", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "Well, we have that video that the President delivered to the military that apparently went out to Armed Forces around the world and an interesting juxtaposition there, Piers, as you're seeing, Congress wrangling with each other and arguing and fighting over whether to fund the government for another six weeks and this whole notion of defunding or delaying ObamaCare.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "have", "that", "video", "that", "the", "President", "delivered", "to", "the", "military", "that", "apparently", "went", "out", "to", "Armed", "Forces", "around", "the", "world", "and", "an", "interesting", "juxtaposition", "there", ",", "Piers", ",", "as", "you", "'re", "seeing", ",", "Congress", "wrangling", "with", "each", "other", "and", "arguing", "and", "fighting", "over", "whether", "to", "fund", "the", "government", "for", "another", "six", "weeks", "and", "this", "whole", "notion", "of", "defunding", "or", "delaying", "ObamaCare", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House", "White House"], "PERSON": ["Jim Acosta"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House of Representatives", "Senate"]}, "docId": "130930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNPS", ",", "RB", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "VBP", "WP", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "Debbie, how do you plead?", "question_tokens": ["Debbie", ",", "how", "do", "you", "plead", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "Well, I plead with my colleagues who really should just go to the floor and let 218 members of the House of Representatives, not only 218 Republicans decide what legislation we are going to send to the Senate and then to the President.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "plead", "with", "my", "colleagues", "who", "really", "should", "just", "go", "to", "the", "floor", "and", "let", "218", "members", "of", "the", "House", "of", "Representatives", ",", "not", "only", "218", "Republicans", "decide", "what", "legislation", "we", "are", "going", "to", "send", "to", "the", "Senate", "and", "then", "to", "the", "President", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "Why aren't they talking?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "n't", "they", "talking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "Well, they're not talking because the only thing the Republicans are willing to talk about is whether or not we are to going to delay or defund or repeal ObamaCare.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "'re", "not", "talking", "because", "the", "only", "thing", "the", "Republicans", "are", "willing", "to", "talk", "about", "is", "whether", "or", "not", "we", "are", "to", "going", "to", "delay", "or", "defund", "or", "repeal", "ObamaCare", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "130930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "Isn't not the way any business gets done?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "not", "the", "way", "any", "business", "gets", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "Look, President Obama has made it very clear that as we implement ObamaCare, which is going to happen, this is a settled matter.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "President", "Obama", "has", "made", "it", "very", "clear", "that", "as", "we", "implement", "ObamaCare", ",", "which", "is", "going", "to", "happen", ",", "this", "is", "a", "settled", "matter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "James Lanksford are you proud of what the Republicans have done tonight?", "question_tokens": ["James", "Lanksford", "are", "you", "proud", "of", "what", "the", "Republicans", "have", "done", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "No, this is the great challenge of this, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "this", "is", "the", "great", "challenge", "of", "this", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James Lanksford"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Are you happy about the shut down tonight?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "happy", "about", "the", "shut", "down", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "No, I'm not happy about it.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "happy", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "We need to have this discussion and if it's so great, what are they afraid of?", "question_tokens": ["We", "need", "to", "have", "this", "discussion", "and", "if", "it", "'s", "so", "great", ",", "what", "are", "they", "afraid", "of", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Well, ObamaCare was of course debated vigorously.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "ObamaCare", "was", "of", "course", "debated", "vigorously", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 358, "question": "Amy, you may not like it but it's called -- Amy?", "question_tokens": ["Amy", ",", "you", "may", "not", "like", "it", "but", "it", "'s", "called", "--", "Amy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "... the election was about ObamaCare...", "answer_tokens": ["...", "the", "election", "was", "about", "ObamaCare", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Is it exactly the same story replayed now 17 years later?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "exactly", "the", "same", "story", "replayed", "now", "17", "years", "later", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "And without that, how do you get anything done?", "question_tokens": ["And", "without", "that", ",", "how", "do", "you", "get", "anything", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Well, I think that's part of it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "part", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "Well, the point I want to make here, is are we dealing though with essentially two quite weak leaders here?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "point", "I", "want", "to", "make", "here", ",", "is", "are", "we", "dealing", "though", "with", "essentially", "two", "quite", "weak", "leaders", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "RB", "CD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "You're the man to us, will we?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "the", "man", "to", "us", ",", "will", "we", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "Well, I think we can again.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "we", "can", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Josh"]}, "docId": "130930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "I think he's jumping in there, Ryan?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "jumping", "in", "there", ",", "Ryan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "EX", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "I think you're being overly optimistic Josh.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "'re", "being", "overly", "optimistic", "Josh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John McCain"]}, "docId": "130930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "Who is that should be given (ph) an election who manages to please everybody?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "that", "should", "be", "given", "(", "ph", ")", "an", "election", "who", "manages", "to", "please", "everybody", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "-NONE-", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Look, I think John McCain's are on their way out and that's the reason why they weren't able to win the presidential election.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "think", "John", "McCain", "'s", "are", "on", "their", "way", "out", "and", "that", "'s", "the", "reason", "why", "they", "were", "n't", "able", "to", "win", "the", "presidential", "election", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130930pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "In all your years, David, in all your experience and all the Congresses you've seen the Senates you've seen and so on, when you put it all together, have you ever known it as bad as this, the actual polarizing between the two camps?", "question_tokens": ["In", "all", "your", "years", ",", "David", ",", "in", "all", "your", "experience", "and", "all", "the", "Congresses", "you", "'ve", "seen", "the", "Senates", "you", "'ve", "seen", "and", "so", "on", ",", "when", "you", "put", "it", "all", "together", ",", "have", "you", "ever", "known", "it", "as", "bad", "as", "this", ",", "the", "actual", "polarizing", "between", "the", "two", "camps", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David"]}}]